Guide to the Ailecia Ruscin Zine Collection, 1994-2002 and undated RL.01120
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Rule of Thumb: Hitchhiking stories, 1999 (Box 10)
  El Toro, CA
- Running with a Lolly, October 1999 (Box 10)
  Los Angeles, CA,
- Runt, no.21, 1994 July (Box 10)
  Merion, PA
- Runt, no.23, 1995 September (Box 10)
- Satellite Whispers, no.1 (Box 10)
- Scam, no.3, 1997 Summer (Box 10)
  Miami, FL: Recess Records
- Scorpion, no.4 (Box 10)
- Screams from Inside, no.6.5 (Box 10)
- Screams from Inside, no.7 (Box 10)
- Selective Living, no.5, 1999 (Box 10)
  Ventura, CA
- Selective Living, no.7, undated (Box 10)
- Self-Defense, no.5 (Box 10)
  Wichita, KS
- SemiBold, no.2, 1997 (Box 10)
- SemiBold, no.3, 1997 (Box 10)
- Shag Stamp, no.8 (Box 10)
  Bradford, United Kingdom
- Shake Bottle Shake (Box 10)
- Sharkpool, no.1, undated (Box 10)
  Kettering, Northamptonshire, United Kingdom
- Shera (Freedom Slut), no.1 (Box 10)
- Shit Pop (Box 10)
  Kyoto, Japan
- Shooting Stars and Midnight Wishes, no.1, undated (Box 10)
- Shredding Paper, no.2, Summer 1999 (Box 10)
  San Rafael, CA
- Silence Through the Noise, no.1, undated (Box 10)
- Silence Through the Noise, no.2, July 1999 (Box 10)
- Sixty, no.5, 1999 October (Box 10)
  Moncton, New Brunswick, Canada
- Slander, no.8, 2000 (Box 10)
  Roseville, MI
- Slander: Former title: Slant, no.7, September 1999 (Box 10)
- Slave, no.5 (Box 10)
  Greensboro, NC
- Slingshot, no.63, Winter 1998 (Box 11)
- Slingshot, no.64, Spring 1999 (Box 11)
- Slingshot, no.69, Summer 2000 (Box 11)
- Slug & Lettuce, no.65, June-August 2000 (Box 11)
- Slug & Lettuce, no.66, Winter 2001 (Box 11)
- Slug & Lettuce, no.67, Spring 2001 (Box 11)
- Slug & Lettuce, no.67, Spring 2001 (Box 11)
- Slug & Lettuce, no.68, Summer 2001 (Box 11)
- SlutWhoreBitch, no.4, April 1999 (Box 11)
  Cincinnati, OH
- Snailmania: refreshment and change (Box 11)
  Chesterfield, MO
- So What?, no.5 (Box 11)
  Littleton, CO
- Sojourner: The Women's Forum, vol. 24, no. 10 (Box 11)
- Solidarity, no.1 (Box 11)
- Some Thoughts About Jack (Box 11)
- Something Like That, no.2, 2000 (Box 11)
  Duluth, GA
- Sour Girl, October 2000 (Box 11)
  Apple Valley, MN,
- Sour Girl, March 2001 (Box 11)
- Spike's Rant, July 2000 (Box 11)
  Ontario, Canada
- Stay Gold, no.6 (Box 11)
- Stick Figure, Summer 1999 (Box 11)
- sticker sisters: catalog, various dates (Box 11)
  Takoma Park, MD
- Stifled, no.6 (Box 11)
- Stitch Witchery, no.2 (Box 11)
- Street Rat, no.2 (Box 11)
- Struggler, no.1 (Box 11)
- Swing Set Grrl, no.1, Winter 2000 (Box 11)
  Levittown, PA
- Tadoussac, June 1999 (Box 11)
- Taking Charge: Abortion and Your Options (Box 11)
- Techno, February 2000 (Box 11)
- Teenage Death Songs, no.11, July 1999 (Box 11)
- Teeny Tiny Robots, no.7 (Box 11)
  Welland, Ontario, Canada
- Terrorist, no.10, Summer 2001 (Box 11)
  Kansas City, KS
- Texttrap, Winter 2000 (Box 11)
- That Girl: (alternatively, That Grrrl), no.7, 1996 (Box 11)
- This is About Suicide, January 1998 (Box 11)
- This World is Broken, no.2 (Box 11)
- Threat Warning (Box 11)
  Assonet, MA
- Three O'Clock (Box 11)
- TIA & Coffee
- To Avoid Suffocation, Jan. 1999 (Box 11)
  Jonesboro, ME
- To Avoid Suffocation, 1999 (Box 11)
- To Avoid Suffocation (Box 11)
- To Avoid Suffocation: The Guts, no.6 (Box 11)
- Tomatoes for Jalapeno (Box 11)
  Florence, SC
- Topical Dictionary of American Government and Politics: The Young Voter's Manual (Box 11)
- Train Grease Panty Line (Box 11)
- Tree of Knowledge (Box 11)
- Truckface, no.6 (Box 11)
- Truly Amazing Gender Aptitude Quiz: What's Your Gender Aptitude?, undated (Box 11)
- Turf: The Zine of Techno Urban Radical Fairies of Washington DC, 1998 (Box 11)
- twat (Box 12)
- Two for the Road: One for you and one for me, Jan. 1999 (Box 12)
  Olympia, WA: The Athena Atlas
- Two Forty A.M., undated (Box 12)
  Atlanta, GA: Lucky 13 Distro
- Underground Publishing Conference (Box 12)
- underpants: pseudo-intellectual, June 2005 (Box 12)
  Auckland, New Zealand: moon rocket distribution
- Valley Girl, no.1 (Box 12)
  Valley, NE
- Valvo, no.1, 1999 February (Box 12)
  Verona, Italy
- Verboslammed (Box 12)
- Version Two Point Oh: It's for You, no.1, 2000 August (Box 12)
- Version Two Point Oh: Keeping a Lookout, no.2, 2000 December (Box 12)
- Vietnam Never Happened, no.7 (Box 12)
- Vortex, July 2000 (Box 12)
  Remuera, Auckland, New Zealand
- Vortex, February 2000 (Box 12)
  Auckland, New Zealand
- Welcome to the Dollhouse, no.8 (Box 12)
- Welcome to the Revolution (Box 12)
- What Rich Jerkface Owned Your Town? (Box 12)
- When I Die… (Box 12)
- Whirling Cervix: Hammering out the Revolution since 1998 (Box 12)
- Whitehead, 2000 (Box 12)
  Famrington, MI
- Whitespace (Box 12)
- Words As Weapons, Winter 2000 (Box 12)
- Words as Weapons, Fall 2000 (Box 12)
- Xerox Debt: The Review Zine with Latent Per-zine Tendencies, no.1, October 1999 (Box 12)
- Xerox Debt: The Review Zine with Latent Per-zine Tendencies, no.3, June 2000 (Box 12)
- Ya Think?, no.3, June-September 1998 (Box 12)
  Oneonta, NY
- Yard Wide Yarns, no.7 (Box 12)
- Youth Quake, 1997 (Box 12)
  Pittsburgh, PA: Pittsburgh Youth Services, INC.
- Zillion Chronicles of Near Love (Box 12)
  Belleville, IL
- Zine Guide, no.2, Winter/Spring 1999 (Box 12)
  Evanston, IL
- Zine Guide, no.3, Winter/Spring 2000 (Box 12)
- Zine Guide, no.4, Fall/Winter 2000 (Box 12)
- Zine Guide, no.5, Fall/Winter 2001 (Box 12)
- Zine Head, 2000 (Box 12)
  Winnipeg, MB, Canada
- Zine World: A Reader's Guide to the Underground Press, no.14, Winter 2000 (Box 12)
  Murfreesboro, TN
- Zine World: A Reader's Guide to the Underground Press, no.15, Spring 2001 (Box 12)
- Zine World: A Reader's Guide to the Underground Press, no.16, Summer 2001 (Box 12)
- Zine World: A Reader's Guide to the Underground Press, no.17, Fall 2001/Winter 2002 (Box 12)
- Zinester's Guide to New York City, July 2000 (Box 12)
- Zinester's Listserv, August 1998 (Box 12)
- Zum, no.12, 1999 (Box 12)